star86.com 2014-03-26

# 

A big Star86 welcome to parents, teachers and other concerned adults. Our website, Star86.com, is hosted by Podscape Holdings Ltd., a New Zealand company with offices at 114 St Georges Bay Rd, Parnell, Auckland 1052, New Zealand. On this site kids can participate in a virtual online environment, giving them the opportunity to explore a virtual universe. With parental permission we also provide kids with the ability to have controlled communications, using limited and moderated chat messages with other kids. In this policy we describe what information we collect, how we collect it, and what we do with it (the policy covers only information collected and used on Star86.com). 

Star86 gives you the ability to have controlled interaction with your friends. We have tried to make this a fun and friendly environment, but the environment on Star86.com also depends on you. Whenever using this site, or any social networking website, you should be careful about the interactions you have with others. 

Podscape Holdings Ltd. strives to comply with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act, (COPPA) a U.S. law that governs the use and collection of information online from kids under 13. To learn more about this law, and about how to protect your kids on interactive online websites, visit the [FTC website](http://www.consumer.ftc.gov/articles/0006-talk-your-kids).

**WHAT INFORMATION WE COLLECT AND HOW WE COLLECT IT**

**Registration**

When users, including children under 13, register and create an account on Star86.com, Podscape Holdings Ltd. asks them to select a screen name, and a password; and to provide his or her parent or guardian's email address for children under 13, the child's age, gender, and country of residence. Users 13 or older will provide their own email address. In the interactive community features, no additional personally identifying information is collected.

In order to use this website, we request certain personally identifiable information from you on the registration form, including a username and password. During registration you are required to give contact information (your parent email address if you are under 13 years of age). We use this information to contact you about the services on our site in which you have expressed interest. Occasionally, Star86.com sends out updates regarding new site features, via parent announcements and our newsletter. We also need to contact you regarding any Customer Service queries you submit, such as password retrieval.

As part of the registration process, we require demographic information (gender, country of residence and birth date); we encourage you to submit this information so we can provide you a more personalized experience. We limit the information we collect, both actively (i.e., what we ask kids) and passively (what we collect through use of web tracking mechanisms like “cookies,”) to that which is necessary for kids to take part in a particular Star86 game activity.

Podscape Holdings Ltd. is the sole owner of the information collected on Star86.com. Podscape Holdings Ltd. collects personally identifiable information from our users at several different points on our website including registration and Customer Service contact queries.

**Orders**

If you purchase a produce or service from us, we request certain personally identifiable information from you on your order form. You must provide contact information (such as name, email address, and shipping address) and financial information (such as credit card information and expiration date). 

**Agents/Service Providers**

We use other third parties such as a shipping company to fulfill orders, and a credit card processing company to bill you for goods and services. We use email and the telephone to assist you if you have questions while using our site or regarding your order. When you sign up for Click n Buy, we will share your email address, country of residence, and Star86 Account ID as necessary for the third party to provide that service. These third parties are prohibited from using your personally identifiable information for promotional purposes. 

**About Cookies**

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user's computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies on this site. We link the information we store in cookies to personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. Cookies are small text files that we place in visitors' computer browsers to store their preferences. Our cookies themselves do not contain any PII. Our cookies reference the PII you provided during registration. We reference the information you provided via an encrypted identifier. Where we link these unique identifiers with your PII, we will treat the unique identifiers as PII as long as they are linked. We use the registration information you provided to: contact you if you lose your password or contact you about site updates and changes. 

We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. We use session cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site. A session ID cookie expires when you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser's “help” file. http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/HTTP_cookie. When a Star86 member is using the site, Star86 collects certain non-personal information by placing and accessing Star86.com cookies on the user's computer. Cookies do not contain any personal information, so we do not use cookies (or other covert or non-consensual methods) to acquire contact information about the user or other users of the computer. 

**Third Party Cookies**

The use of cookies by our affiliates and/or service providers is not covered by our privacy statement. We do not have access or control over these cookies. Our affiliates or service providers use session ID cookies to provide demographic and metrics information to Podscape Holdings Ltd. and to make it easier for you to navigate our site, in order for you to use the subscription service. 

**How Star86 Uses the Information it Collects**

Star86 uses the parent or guardian's email address provided at registration to notify parents that their kids have created an account on Star86.com. In that initial notice, parents are provided a link to this privacy policy, and details about how their kids can use Star86.com. Parents are required to provide their consent before their kid's accounts can be activated. Parent email addresses are used to communicate with parents about their kids in relation to their activity at Star86.com such as a forgotten password. Upon activation of an account, the information submitted will be used by Star86 to create a personalized avatar and will allow the registered user to participate on the Star86.com website, which contains a variety of interactive community features. Within those features, users are identified in the community by their screen name, age, gender and country of origin. This limited (and non-personal) identifying information, accompanied by a picture of their avatar, will be displayed to the user or kid's friends and other users of the site. If you want to read more about how our site operates, we encourage you to read our Parent's Page. 

**Parental Rights**

Parents and legal guardians of kids under 13 who are members of Star86.com have certain rights under COPPA, and Star86 recognizes those rights. Parents/guardians can consent to collection and use of a kid's personally identifiable information (PII) without consenting to the disclosure of information to third parties. Currently the only identifiable information we collect from children is the parent email address. We will not knowingly register children under 13 years old on Star86.com without parental consent. Without consent, a child under 13 cannot use any of the community features. If a parent does not provide consent, we will delete the information provided during the registration process within a reasonable time period. 

A child's participation or access to an activity on our site is not conditioned on their providing more Personal Information than is reasonably necessary for the activity. Parents/guardians can review information their children have contributed to Star86.com, request that Star86 delete that information, and refuse to allow Star86 to collect further information from their kids by contacting our Customer Services department by email at support@Star86.com. Parents should include their kid's username and the registered (parent's) email address in the email so we can better assist them with their inquiry or request. Star86 may ask additional questions or take other steps to verify the identity of parents/guardians before responding to a request to review or delete their kid's information, or a request to refuse further collection from kids. 

**Links to Third Party Websites**

We provide links to third party websites, including links from our “Buy Stuff” feature. Through that feature, we let our users know where they can purchase Star86 merchandise. Before a player can exit our website, we explain that the player is leaving our website, and going to the website of a third party. Once they leave our site, he or she may submit information to a third party, over whom we have no authority or control, and who may have different information collection and use practices. Users and Parents/guardians should always read a company's privacy policy carefully, including those companies to whom we provide links, before submitting information to them. 

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**

Star86 does not share, rent or trade personally identifying information about our registered users, including kids under 13, with non-affiliated third parties (i.e., companies who are not one of our corporate affiliates or who are not providing support to the internal operations of our company) for their promotional purposes. Star86 makes every reasonable effort to disallow and discourage users and kids from sharing personally identifying information with each other via the community features via a filter system and live moderators. The only information that can be openly shared in the Star86.com community features are screen names (and kids are cautioned not to select their real names), country of residence, age, gender and moderated messages. Users and kids who use the pin board features do have the opportunity to draft their own messages to their friends, but we do not prompt any site users to provide any identifying information about themselves. Star86 may share other information submitted on its site - non-personal information - to provide requested products or services, if permission is granted, or under the following circumstances: We share personal information in certain cases in order to prevent, take action against or investigate situations regarding illegal activities, fraud or suspected fraud, events in which threats or potential threats to the physical safety of any person or persons is evident, when violations of Star86's terms of use occur, or in other situations required by law. We respond to subpoenas, court orders and other legal processes, or make use of information in exercising our legal rights or establishing defense against legal claims. We transfer information about users if Star86 is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, Star86 notifies the user in advance of any information transfer and before it may become subject to any other privacy policy. We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site. 

**Community Disclosures**

If you use a forum or blog on this Web site, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of these forums, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. Though we pre-moderate the blog comments and the Forums are pre-moderated and post-moderated, we are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these forums.

**Opting Out**

If you no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional communications, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each newsletter or you may communicate by emailing us at support@Star86.com - please type UNSUBSCRIBE in the subject line, or you may contact us in writing by posting your mail to: Star86, PO Box 911345, Victoria Street West, Auckland 1142, New Zealand, to opt-out. 

**Updating/Accessing/Amending/Correcting Personally Identifiable Information**

If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, amend, delete/remove or deactivate it by emailing our Customer Support at support@Star86.com or by contacting us by postal mail at the contact information listed below. We will respond to your request to change the information within 3 days. 

**Confidentiality and Security**

Information a user or child submits to Star86.com that relates to his or her account is password-protected. No employee of Star86 nor any automated system will contact a user or parent by email or messaging systems asking for a user or child's login details, password or any other personal information related or unrelated to a Star86 service or product. If any message claiming or appearing to come from Star86 or any of its related websites is sent to you asking for such information, please report it immediately to support@Star86.com. 

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personally identifiable information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can send email us at support@Star86.com. 

Podscape Holdings Ltd. complies with the EU Safe Harbor framework as set forth by the Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of data from the European Union. 

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

Space exploration is a challenging process, and in order to ensure the players are looked after properly and their owners kept stimulated, the practices of Star86.com may alter from time to time. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the home page, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. 

If we make material changes to how we collect and use Personal Information from children under age 13, we will notify parents by email in order to obtain verifiable parental consent for the new uses of the child's Personal Information. 

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page. 

**Questions and Suggestions**

If you have questions or suggestions, please [contact us](http://www.star86.com/help/contact) or mail us at: attn: Customer Service, Star86, PO Box 911345, Victoria St West, Auckland, New Zealand.
